Ali Eren Kayhan

Game Developer and Designer

ali_erenbatman@hotmail.com | +90 (530) 964 98 44 github.com/Alierenkayhan | linkedin.com/in/alierenkayhan

Personal website: alierenkayhan.github.io

Gungoren, Istanbul, Turkey

SUMMARY

Game developer with 1 year of experience creating 2D and 3D indie games in different areas (instructional, horror, etc.) for PC with Unity and senior student at Boğaziçi University Computer and Instructional Technologies teaching, developed projects and uploaded on my GitHub account and itch.io account.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

2017 – 2024 **Boğaziçi University**, Istanbul, Turkey

Department of Computer Education and Educational Technology

2022 - 2023 Bremen University, Bremen, Germany

Department of Digital Media

Erasmus Exchange Scholarship Program

2022 – 2023 Tuncay Azaphan A.T.M. HIGH School, Istanbul, Turkey

Information Technologies / Web Programming

- Grade average: 86,78
- Graduated, Rank 1
- Team member in Basketball, Chess, Knowledge Contest, Shot Put

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Unity, Build 2D and 3D games, C#, MSSQL, GIT, HTML, CSS, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Cisco Package Tracer, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Canva, Font Awesome, Figma, Bootstrap, Game Development, Game Design

CORE COMPETENCIES

Project Management, Product Management, Documentation, Lifelong learner, Coordinating a team, Team worker, Creating instructional materials

LANGUAGE

English B2, German A2, Turkish Native Speaker

PROJECTS

2022 - Atölye, Game Developer

Development activities;

- Developed a 2D instructional game in Unity
- Taught Grade 6 Mathematics Angles and Area Measurement
- Published on Friday, June 10, 2022 on itch.io

2022 - Wer lst Der Mörder?, Game Developer

Development activities;

- Developed a 2D instructional game in Unity
- Taught one of the German Grammar rules, "Relativsätze im Nominative"
- Assist by Bige Kolukısa Inelmen who is an academician at Boğaziçi University
- Published on Sunday, Apr 17, 2022 on itch.io

2022 - The Virus Game Developer

Development activities;

- Developed a 3D horror game in Unity
- Solo game developer
- Published on Thursday, Feb 10, 2022 on itch.io

Development log activities;

 Demo version 0.2 game and development log published on Monday, Aug 29, 2022 on itch.io

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - Indie Game Developer

Development activities:

- Create 2D-3D games in different types with Unity
- · Publish on itch.io and GitHub

2020 - EduTech - Boğaziçi University Education and Technology Community,

President From 2022

Development activities;

- Build a website
- Build a simulation
 - o Published on itch.io
 - o Published on Boun-Edutech GitHub and my GitHub
- Arrange social media accounts and other accounts
- Prepare an introduction video for the new EduTech administration
- Arrange and plan events and talks

Member From 2020

Development activities;

- Proposed club logo design
- Proposed club activities' poster design

2017 - 2018 COMPEC - Boğaziçi University Informatics Club, Team member

Responsibility;

- Corresponded with Airbar firm for Techsummit 18
- Provided registration and guided people
- Guided people in the Insider Firm Tour and took photos

INTERNSHIP

Sept 2016 - Nov 2016 Yıldız Teknik University, Intern (3 Month Full Time)

Internship under the control of Assistant Professor Doctor Ziya Cihan Tayşi Responsibility;

Arranged cable of laboratory

Development activities;

Designed a plan for a laboratory in Adobe Fireworks

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

2022 - Ted Talks Translator, Translator

Development activities;

- Translate Ted Talks videos as a volunteer
- A youtube playlist to reach TED videos that I translated on my website

2022 - Not Tutuyoruz,

Editor From 2022

Development activities;

· Checking blogs written English

Content Writer From 2022

Development activities;

· Publish blogs about different topics on Medium

CERTIFICATIONS

gram

MEMBERSHIP

2020 –	Team Member From 2020 and President From 2022
2020 –	Boğaziçi University Atletizm Club, Team Member in Shot Put
2017 – 2018	Boğaziçi University Informatics Club (COMPEC), Team Member

BLOG PUBLICATIONS

2022 Creating University Network System In Cisco Packet Tracer, Instruction

- Optimize university network topologies and imitate modern computer networks.
- Stimulate the topology in Cisco Packet Tracer
- · Collaborate to document our strategy

Published on Blogger, Medium, and Patika Dev

2022 Energy plan for German, Sustainability

- Systematized energy optimism and algorithms for Germany
- Explained a proposal for the process and presentation of a new energy plan for Germany
- Calculated in the direction of the demand and supply concerned reducing CO2 emissions at the macro level
- Optimized to reduce CO2 emissions
- Designed to decrease CO2 emissions by 70% in 2040, compared to 1990
- Published on Saturday, 18 June 2022 on Blogger

2022 SQL Pizza Company Database, Database, and MSSQL

- Optimized class diagram
- Built a database
- Documented business rules and the project Published on Wednesday, 15 June 2022 on Blogger

2021 Arduino

 Designed and manufactured single-board microcontrollers and microcontroller kits for building digital devices
Published on Saturday, 12 December 2020 on Blogger

2021 Unity AR

- Built an interactive experience of a real-world environment where the objects that reside in the real world are enhanced by computergenerated perceptual information
- Published on Thursday, 14 January 2021 on Blogger

2021 VEX Robotics, Programming Robots, and VEX Robotics

- Programmed robots in stem labs
- Published on Saturday, January 9, 2021 on Blogger

HOBBY

- 10 bronze, 6 silver, and 2 gold medals from sports.
- Judo (2. dan judo black belt, 1. level judo assistant coach, more than 10 years)
- Basketball
- Chess
- Playing saz
- Solving the Rubik's Cube and Megamix